<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Tooltips> 


    <Open_Folder>Left click to browse for a file, 
right click to open the selected file.</Open_Folder>   
    
    <Open_Backup>Left click while button is red to open parent 
directory. Left click while green to open directory of selected backup.

Right click to open Axe_Info.txt of the selected Backup.</Open_Backup>  
  
    <Toggle_List>Click to toggle the List of Instances
in the selected Xml.</Toggle_List>
    <Remove_Backup>Green means there is no Backup selected,
that you could delete. Red means delete the selected Backup.</Remove_Backup>
    
    <Backup>Toggle Backup Mode</Backup>    
    <Undo>Undo the last changes and remove the corresponding auto backup.</Undo>   
    
    <Search>If the parent name text box is selected, 
browse the whole xml directory for nodes of this name.
If attribute name text box is selected we search the selected file for an entity with that attribute value.</Search>
    <Merge_Backups>Left click a backup (green) to merge its whole branch.

Left click multiple backups while holding the shift key (red) to merge
the selected Backups into their base backup.</Merge_Backups> 
       
    <Set_Attribute>Click to toggle between name of the Attribute (black) and its value (white).</Set_Attribute>
    <Checkout>Checkout the selected Backup.
This loads it into your working directory.

If you checkout older backups it will overwrite new changes in the working directory.</Checkout>
        
        
    <Percent>While in Percent Mode, Xml Axe gets the original values of the selected tag.
And it scales them either UP or DOWN by the specified amount of %.
                                        
If no certain unit is selected, and no Type Filter is set, this percent balancing will be applied to all entities that have the selected tag.</Percent>
    <Script>Toggle Script mode</Script>    
    <Operator>Inverts from + to - and the other way around when pressed.
You can select "True" in the drop down box to switch into bool mode, 
or move the track bar below to get back to numbers.</Operator>
    <Add_Backup>Create a new Backup of the current working directory.</Add_Backup>   
    <Axe>Run Xml Axe for the settings in the text boxes.
A prompt asks which files should be edited and automatically creates a backup of these files before applying their changes.</Axe>
    <Settings>Toggle settings mode</Settings>
    <Run>Starts a program and its parameters, 
if they are defined in the Settings. 

Otherwise if in EAW mode, it will seek to lauch the mod of the selected xml.</Run>
    <Reset>Reset all settings to their default state. 
Caution, this will erase all custom xml tags you wrote.</Reset>



</Tooltips>

